# Juan Francisco Perez

"I've been passionate about computers since I was a kid. I have always been a very curious and self-taught person. I have participated in several projects since my time as a student and after finishing my degree. I have experience as SysAdmin, and SRE as Coordinator of Technical and Administrative Teams."

Gorriti 213 7th floor 4600 San Salvador de Jujuy. +(54) 3884802323 yojota@gmail.com https://yojota.cloud

#### **Main Skills**

GNU/Linux system administrator, Cloud Computing (AWS, Azure), and deep knowledge in computer science.

## **Experiences**

## **Voolkia to mercado libre**: DevOps Engineer.

November 2021 - April 2022

Platform - Fundations Team. Admin multi cloud account. K8s. Ansible. Cloud Formation. Scripting - Infrastructure Level 1

## **Globant**: DevOps Engineer.

November 2021 - April 2022

CI/CD. Jenkins. Bash scripting. AWS infrastructure. In the account Stride (USA client).

## **Silentium Apps**: SRE - DevOps

July 2021 - October 2021

CI/CD in docker environment. AWS - Azure - On-premise. Jenkins. Github Action.

## **Edrans**, Buenos Aires: Site Operation.

September of 2020 - June 2021

The first point of contact to external worldwide customers, also you will be helping to identify, analyze and resolve first-tier technical issues on large-scale productive platforms.

#### **Projects**

## **NicromIT:** Cloud Solutions – DevOps Culture.

CEO. In charge of customer contact. Project manager. Sysadmin Linux. DevOps Team Support

### **Strengths**

Restless

Good teamwork

Good communication

Ease to communicate with non-technical equipment.

#### **Additional Activities**

**Proyecto Pachado** Secure Wifi connection with certificates 2011

**Founder:** Grupo de usuarios de software libre de Jujuy.

**Tutor:** Introduction to free software. Duration 1 year.

**Exhibitor and Speaker:** In different free software events in the province and throughout the country.

#### Languages

Spanish (native).

English (intermediate B1).

#### **Education**

## Universidad Catolica de Santiago del Estero: IT Engineering

March of 2003 - November del 2011 Complete

Technical Skills	
Sysadmin GNU Linux	***
Scripting python, bash, php	***
Docker	***
Kubernetes	**
Terraform (IaaC)	***
AWS	***
Google Cloud	*
Virtualization	***
Management Tools and Project (Trello, Jira, Zenkit, Confluence, etc)	******
Microsoft environment	**
Ansible	*
Git	***
Github Action	***
Jenkins	**
Powershell	*
Deploy Experience (node, angular, and .Net)	***
Azure	**
Certifications	
AWS APN	Finished
AWS Cloud Particioner	In progress

I have been **working remotely** for more than three years. I have experience working at night shift. In the last few years, I have worked with clients around the world (APAC and AMER).